I’m from Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky, where are you from
Я из Украины город Хмельницкий Вы откуда
and the mistakes in the Belgorod region are
и ошибки на Белгородской области
not just everything there, from somewhere in Rostov,
не просто все там откуда-то с Ростова
I start Shchebekina. I’m from Belgorod, like a
начинают я щебекина Я с Белгорода типа
joke,
прикол такое
this can happen in real Shebekino.
может такое быть в реальной Шебекино
city ​​council of Shebekino I
городской совет Шебекино
won’t say the
не скажу
crossroads, you’re crossing the river,
перекресток прямо речку переезжаешь
look at the
смотрите
street Yes, on the street And these without a street,
улица какая Да на улице А эти без улицы
I don’t even tell you yet.
я вам даже Пока нет вы не себе Когда вы
they came
приезжали
because you were going there But if you
потому что вот вы ехали туда Но если вы
lived in Shebekino you would know I don’t want to
жили в Шебекино вы бы знали Я не хочу
just name the streets
просто улицы называть
if you lived in Shebekino you would know
если бы вы жили в Шебекино вы бы знали
Explain why Putin cannot protect
Объясните почему Путин не может защитить
your Shebekino
ваши Шебекино
why Putin cannot protect Everything is
почему Путин не может защитить Все
burned out
подгорел
I don’t have time
я не успеваю
why  Putin can’t protect
почему Путин не может защитить
Tell me why after he can’t protect
Скажите почему после не может защитить
evacuation of what in Belgorod then sit
эвакуация чего в Белгороде тогда сидите
if they are in Shebekino while I have an apartment
если они в Шебекино пока у меня квартира
here apartment Why don’t you sit in the apartment
тут квартира А что квартире не сидите
now
сейчас
Why can’t the path be made so that
А почему пути не может сделать так чтобы
it is safe
было безопасно
many questions  I’ll ask you Let’s
много вопросов Можно я вам задам
try that there Khmelnitsky
Попробуйте давайте что там Хмельницкого
in general everything exploded
вообще все взорвалась
so shorter 6 7th floor again like an
так короче 6 7 этаже снова как
earthquake 3 points was And that it
землетрясение 3 балла было А что она так
burned there somehow for so long
долго там как-то горело
that an underground wave exploded there
что там взорвались подземные
like this up
волна вот так наверх
the whole city No [ __ ]
всем городом Ни хрена себе
pollution plus we are like that too  measured with
загрязнения плюс мы так тоже мерили
such Geiger counters In short, everything is
такими счетчиками Гейгера Короче все
fine, like everything is normal here
нормально типа тут абсолютно все норме
Yes, but the Poles did something there That’s all I
Да но поляки что-то там поступили Это
’ll tell you, see yours tell
все расскажу смотри ваши рассказывают
More Romania These are all your fables,
Больше Румынии Это все ваши басни так
it’s all a circus in short, now the main
это все цирк короче теперь главный
question was not fired at Shchebekin before the start of the special operation
вопрос до начала спецоперации щебекина
Yes, Putin began
не обстреливали Да Путин начал
a special operation  to protect the Donbass And now he
спецоперацию по защите Донбасса А теперь
didn’t defend the Donbass And they also started
не защитил Донбасс А еще начали
shelling the Belgorod region Why
обстреливать Белгородской области Почему
so Well, how to live there the guys who
так Ну как там жить ребята которых
were defeated in the Donbass, they scattered along the
разбили на Донбассе они рассыпались по
entire front line and now how these climb
всей линии фронта и теперь как эти лезут
where they will find a hole why why Putin
где дырку найдут почему почему Путин не
cannot do so that there is no hole
может делать так чтобы не было дырки
you want to say that your
вы хотите сказать что у вас там
city of 40,000 was left there without a
40-тысячный город был оставлен без
garrison without any kind of protection,
гарнизона без какой-то охраны
and they were right on the way to this point,
а они они прямо по дороге к этому пункту
which
который таможенному прям оперли Я не
they directly opened to the customs.
понюхать они прямо по дороге ехали на
point And they started to shoot armored personnel carriers from
пункт А их начали расстреливать БТР с
these they burned the suns there today
этих пожгли там солнцепеков сегодня
they showed they put it
показывали положили
if they destroyed it at the border So then they
если уничтожали на границе Так что тогда
broke through there
прорвался туда
nothing saves
ничего не спасает
your shebekina
ваше шебекина
these fairy tales there form is not a form but as a
вот эти сказки там форма не форма но в
result of Shebekino [ __ ] spread people are
результате Шебекино нахрен разносят люди
being evacuated from there your marauders
оттуда эвакуируются там ваши мародёры
already this video  watched the girls What is
уже это видео смотрел девочки Что такое
this hashtag they launched Shchebekino - this is
вот этот хэштег запустили щебекино - это
Russia like protect us Putin and Putin
Россия типа защитите нас Путин а Путин
cannot protect Why is it so everyone has already
не может защитить Почему так так все уже
thrown everyone out Who didn’t have time to escape
все всех выкинули Кто не успел убежать
killed me correctly I understood correctly that
убили я правильно Я правильно понял что
people have already returned to Shebekino already
люди Уже вернулись в Шебекино уже
no evacuation is
эвакуации нет
coming back Yes  And you When you return
возвращается Да А вы Когда вернетесь
Well, when you return shebekin
Ну вы когда вернете шебекина
[laugh]
[смех]
not stupid not stupid I agree
не тупой не тупой согласен
Just you say that everything is fine to me
Просто вы говорите что мне всё нормально
already people are coming back You
уже люди возвращаются
see yes, that is,
пахнет Вот видите да то есть то есть
Russia does not protect shebeki pressed
Россия не защищает шебеки нажал
somewhere a rocket will bang and you
где-то бахнет ракета и вы под стол
will crawl under the table  I’ll also climb under labor
полезете я полезу тоже под труда
Look, I’m not going to say that no, we
Смотри я не буду говорить что нет у нас
protected Khmelnitsky from shelling, like
защитили Хмельницкий от обстрелов типа
everything here won’t fly in,
всё тут ничего не прилетит
I absolutely understand, yes, we have
я абсолютно понимаю да что типа у нас
flights and there are arrivals,
прилетает и прилёты есть да Всё обсудим
we’ll discuss everything, we understand everything in all cities, we
мы это все понимаем во всех городах мы
tolerate Yes, because  what do we know for the sake of why
терпим Да потому что мы знаем ради чего
we are going to this Victory Yes, that's why
мы идём к этой Победе Да вот ради чего
Shebekino type Was given to be torn to pieces by
Шебекино типа Отдали на растерзание
Ukrainians, or rather not to Ukrainians, but to the
украинцами а точнее не украинцам а
Russian
российскому добровольскому
volunteer corps and the legion freedom
добровольскому корпусу и легиону свобода
of Russia civil war they are Citizens of the
России гражданская война они Граждане
Russian Federation
Российской Федерации
that Yes drive began
что Да драйване начал начался
breakthroughs started talking as soon as the first
прорывки разговаривал как только первый
day  A breakthrough has begun all Ukrainians jumping
день Начался прорыв все украинцы прыгали
here with chairs shouting
тут со стульями кричали
all Ukrainians
все украинцы
[music]
[музыка]
we are about them And who are the dead Show me it’s not
мы о них А кто эти убитые Покажите я не
just a
просто это
fake about some dead No to
фейк про каких-то убитых Нет
me all Russians start
мне все мне все россияне начинают
telling me fables that they killed there So wait
говорить басни что там убили Так подожди
tell me where I can see
скажите где могу посмотреть
tell me where I can see that
скажите где могу посмотреть что в
these types of rebels were killed in hayvoron
гайвороне убили этих типа
In the sense they refused How it is done
В смысле отказались Как делается на
officially Yes look at officially
официально Да смотрите на официально у
we have such a policy at the official level of
нас такая политика на официальном уровне
the state says they are not there like this is
государства говорит их там нет типа это
not our feature since 2014 So we
не наша это фишка с 2014 года Так мы
just found out that this is possible  and we all
просто узнали что так можно и мы все
understand that this is who it is, yes,
понимаем что это кто это да ну
officially, we say No, these are some kind of
официально мы говорим Нет это какие-то
Russian volunteer corps and the Legion of
русские добровольские корпуса и Легион
Freedom of Russia, then I’ll say yes When they
Свободы России дальше скажу да Когда
take Belgorod, yes, that is, we
будут брать Белгород да то есть мы тоже
will also say this is some kind of Russian
будем говорить это какой-то русский
volunteer corps, they
добровольческий корпус они
found it out of the auction  but now you
вон торгах нашли но сейчас в любом
can buy a howitzer in any military store, for example, a howitzer
военторге можно купить например гаубица
there Storm Shadow is shorter than hummers and like I
там Шторм Shadow короче hummers и типа я
tell you really it’s like this when there
вам говорю реально это такой вот когда
will be arrivals in Belgorod such as in
будет прилеты по Белгороду такие как по
Shebekino I will also get high I will
Шебекино я тоже буду кайфовать я буду
say [ __ ] Belgorod evacuation
говорить [__] Белгород эвакуация
let’s not sleep in short I’m when here in
давай не спи короче я когда вот в
last year, the first arrivals in Belgorod
прошлом году первые прилеты по Белгороду
were such a thought, a badge Is it all
были я такой думал бляха Неужели всё это
good if it’s not yours, but these are
хорошо если это не ваши нет а это
some kind of Volunteers Yes, look
какие-то Добровольцы Да смотри
yes yes The
да да
enemy of my enemy my friend
Враг моего врага мой друг
I’m just excited from this information
Я просто возбуждён от этой информации
then it dries up you dries up I
потом пересыхает у вас пересыхает я
say so much yes  it dries up So it
столько говорю да отсохнет Так что
just
просто капец да
dries up Yes, in short, it dries up at all Yes, everything from
сохнет Да короче вообще сохнет Да все из
your end dries up to me endlessly
концом у вас сохнет у меня без конца
dries up to your end dries up to the
сохнет у вас концом сохнет
end hold on to your
за конец держитесь
native topic, you know it all when
родная тема это всех знаешь когда
the Russians burn it starts to cross at the end
русские подгорает начинает на конце
now I laugh
теперь Я посмеюсь
so that's when they started to bomb  Squirrels, but
так вот когда начали бомбить Белках но
all of Russia will now respond with a nuclear strike,
все Россия сейчас ответит ядерный удар
now everyone understands that Russia can be
теперь все поняли что Россию можно
bombed
бомбить
first by sabotage and then 100 missiles
сначала диверсия и потом 100 ракет
flew
полетела
false before that, it also flew so much
неправда до этого также столь летела
you will tell some fables of Krylov, you
ты расскажешь какие-то басни Крылова
understand
понимаешь
a woman in the village, you will just come up with
женщина в деревне ты ты придумаешь
some fables on the go I
просто какие-то басни на ходу Я тебе
I’m telling you from Ukraine, how the rockets flew, they
говорю я из Украины ракеты как летели
fly, that is, not only because of
таки летают то есть не только что вот
Bryansk, shelling began, you
из-за Брянска началась обстрел вы на
shoot regardless of this Bryansk is not
стреляйте независимо от этого Брянск не
Bryansk Maybe you understand morons That’s the
Брянске Может вы [__] понимаешь Вот
finished morons invaders
[__] [__] оккупанты
And yesterday the day before yesterday they began to look Where are
А вчера позавчера начали искать Где же
the bomb shelters that
бомбоубежища который
Kiev knows  Since last year, Kiev knows
Киев знает Киев с прошлого года знает
where the bomb shelters are, it just
где бомбы убежища просто
happened that people ran across
случилось ситуация что люди перебежали
the bomb shelter and the watchman did not open
бомбоубежище а сторож не открыл
the bomb shelter, so all this became a
бомбоубежище вот и всё это стало
media situation, and look,
медийная ситуация причём Смотри
look
смотри
No, this is my brother
Нет это мой брат
blogger Yes,
блогер да
one dog is a couple Yes, we just take Well,
одна собака пара Да мы просто брать Ну у
I don’t have time so much  like he's a
меня нет времени так сильно типа он
Streamer like he's sitting there on this blog to
Стример типа он там сидит в это блоге
shoot sometimes I go out to neigh
снимать я иногда так Выхожу поржать
the Russians it's chattering to say you
русских это забалтываете сказать ничего
don't give anything it's our tactic
не даете это наша тактика
openers Just professional yes yes like that
сошники Просто профессиональные да да
and that's all yes look it turns out The bottom line is
вот так и все да посмотрите получается
that a year ago no one else
Суть в том что год назад никто иной не
thought about the bombing  Shebekin and Belgorod
думал про бомбежки шебекина и Белгорода
And now, in short, rich Klitschko.
А теперь короче богатых Кличко
I want to tell you to explain what you explained
Я хочу рассказать вот объяснить что вы
to me. How is it that
мне объяснили Как так получается что
Putin cannot or does not want to protect him?
Путин не может или не хочет защитить он
we are weak we are
мы слабые государство мы слабенькая мы
small without such power you are the second you are the
маленькая без такой мощи вы вторая вы
second army of the world how did it happen that
вторая армия мира как так получилось что
you attacked our country by doing a
вы напали на нашу страну сделав
special operation to protect the Donbass you can’t
спецоперацию по защите Донбасса не
defend now some [ __ ]
можете защитить теперь какой-то сраный
Belgorod it’s just just a circus I just
Белгород это просто просто цирк просто я
don’t know you are already laughing stupidly America
не знаю с вас уже ржёт тупо Америка
generally burns I have a friend he is a
вообще жжет У меня друг знакомый он
Marine in the USA so he tells me
Морпех в США так он мне говорит
[music]
[музыка]
The only thing they can't hang is a
Единственное что они не могут завис
fly-babble
бляха-муха